Sam Mans

smans.tech@gmail.com My Portfolio | GitHub | Linkedin

About Me

A web developer with experience supporting mobile applications and web-based solutions

Skills and Tools

Web Development

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Node, SCSS Bootstrap, GIT, Github

Content Management Systems

WordPress, Drupal

Software and Services

VSCode, Google Analytics, Hootsuite, Tableau, Mailchimp, Image Editing Software

Workflow

JIRA, Slack, Basecamp

Relevant Work Experience

Web Developer and Marketing Consultant, Syyrup - RBKJ

(September 2017 to Present)

- Assisting in the development, analytics, social media and marketing for <u>Syyrup</u>, a positive news application
- Working with the developer and content team to create new content, add functionality, generate performance reports, design promotional pages and manage social media content
 Angular 2+ | Ionic | GitHub | Analytics | Social Media | Digital Marketing

Assistant Manager, Technology and Research, M2 Health Care Consulting (February 2016 - Present)

- Managing the M2 Healthcare Consulting <u>website</u>, creating site content, installing plugins, troubleshooting technical issues and adding additional functionality such as analytics and MailChimp
- Assisting in the production of health care policy research reports, presentations and other materials for M2 clients

Website Management | HTML/CSS | WordPress | CPanel | Technical Support

Web Migration and Production Assistant, National Association of Realtors (August 2017 - December 2017)

- Working as part of NAR's web production and migration team migrating old site content to the new Drupal 7 website <u>nar.realtor</u>
- Working with departments countrywide to publish digital content, troubleshooting site-wide issues, attending daily stand-up meetings and testing site changes prior to release

 $Drupal \mid Jira \mid HTML/CSS \mid JavaScript \mid Quality \ Assurance \mid Technical \ Support$

Volunteer Work and Projects

Website Manager | Festival Afro-Bahia | December 2016 - July 2018

Website Manager for <u>Festival Afro-Bahia</u> - WordPress Management, Photo Editing and Scheduling

Education, Certifications and Coursework

B.S.B.A Marketing | Suffolk University, Boston, MA

- Concentration in Marketing and Information Systems Management

A+ Certification | COMPTIA

- Computer technician certification for computer installation, troubleshooting, and support